import { Question } from "./type";

export const questionBank: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: ".SDRAWKCAB NOITSEUQ SIHT REQSNA",
    possibleAns: ["KO", "What?", "I don't understand", "Backwards"],
    correctAns: "KO",
  },
  {
    question: "The answer is REALLY big",
    possibleAns: ["ANSWER", "REALLY Big", "âˆž", "Whale"],
    correctAns: "Whale",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "What was the answer to question 2?",
    possibleAns: ["This one", "That one", "This?", "Definitely this"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
  {
    question: "Can a match box?",
    possibleAns: ["Yes", "No", "No, but a tin can", "Yes, one beat Mike Tyson"],
    correctAns: "No, but a tin can",
  },
];
